# NUTTANICHA TECHANORARAJ

## JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

086-8811209

nutthanicha4@gmail.com

sdnt-portfolio.vercel.app

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

I am a Junior Software Developer from Generation Thailand, skilled in HTML, CSS, TailwindCSS, JavaScript, React, NodeJS, Postman and GIT. Before this, I worked as a Medical Technician for over four years, which sparked my interest in the software used in hospitals and the automated machines that process patient results.

My passion for gaming, technology, and fulfilling my childhood dream led me to pursue software development.

I look forward to working together. Although I'm new to this field, my past experience has given me strong teamwork skills, the ability to work under pressure, punctuality, attention to detail, adaptive learning and a positive attitude.

#### **SKILLS**

**Technical Skills:** SQL, HTML, CSS, TailwindCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, NodeJS, MongoDB, Git, GitHub, Postman, Figma, Vercel, Render

Behavioral Skills: Time Management, Teamwork, Patience, Orientation to detail, Growth mindset, Positive attitude

Language Skills: Thai (Native speaker), English (TOEIC = 730)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **GENERATION THAILAND BOOTCAMP**

(September 2024 - December 2024)

#### Junior software developer (Cohort 8)

- · Learned how to build web application with React + Vite (Frontend), NodeJS (Backend) and MongoDB (Database)
- Final Project (4 Members): Application Game E-Commerce using MERN Stack CRUD Operations
  - Managed projects using Trello and Confluence.
  - Worked as a team and consulted on issues.
  - Problem-Solving and Critical Thinking
  - Experience with Agile Development Practices
  - Learning to Work with Version Control (Git)

# FACULTY OF ALLIED HEALTH SCIENCES, CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY

(2021 - 2022)

#### Medical technologist

- · Collected and prepared specimens and performed laboratory procedures.
- · Verified, recorded, and reported lab results on all performed tests.
- Monitored and maintained laboratory equipment, and troubleshot and resolved instrument problems.
- · Performed quality control tests to ensure the accuracy of results

### **EDUCATION**

RANGSIT UNIVERSITY (2013 - 2017)

**Bachelor Degree of Science (Medical Technology)**